[Music]
Estimated Expected Value
Expected
k with the representation of policy
every
I told you want you policy was d very
first class right as
you actions and action probability
sorry
and it could be some kid ka a
probability distribution bike
changing this policy over time true date
eventuality I bill b recommend with
probability one you pull the
best of right
so this policy is going you cup changing
what time
party in direct fashion
of d writing it on soft apps
probability 80 equal
you this additional roshan bill b you think
non approach some
kid of
policy search approach right so let late
cup it simple I bill talk about an
you action how right and give they
can talk about other things like so very
very simplified situation which is called an
binary bin it where are you get one
you give you like historical perspectively
okay so in fact
in addition you d go read of jo off  This
discussion in d book right so you want u no more about
d kid of things I am talking about right no way have u to go back
and read
edition one
alpha small enough so the
best action relationship convert
this problems comes right and what about the
basis how if this is this I am
doing this
reaction
some other action this prime what should I do it should be
b plus alpha times zero minus
brother so this is u actions multiple actions
what happens if not b
a probability
distribution I like u make sir date everything
stage a probability
distribution
weds multiple actions have taking right now
alpha from everybody
actions okay so dat when d sum of everything after dat also it will b
one
starting of sussumption you one so I need u
make sir five t plus one also
according okay so pretty
sir which of you can do the correct
adjustment so this is essential
and what  Happens IF
1.0
The nothing you do with d reward
OK
In fact
Dat
IF
D probability
I would like this
Dat
IF
D probability
I would like this
Dat
IF
D probability
I would like this
Probability you be one
You remember the
form of d rule
I told you
Right
Current
form of d rule
I told you
Right
Current
form of d rule
I told you
Right
Current
value
Target minus se current value
So error
Right
Target minus se current value
So error
Right
Target minus se current value
So error
Right
So current value plus alpha times error
So
date
I think se way
Her d probability
date
I think se way
Her d probability
date
I think se way
Her d probability
I want is zero
OK
So it's n
I want is zero
OK
So it's n
I want is zero
OK
So it's n
current value plus
alpha times zero minus pi
So simplified
Dat
I know it's one
Minus
Dat
I know it's one
Minus
Dat
I know it's one
Minus
writing it is d se form
Right
So one
It's
writing it is d se form
Right
So one
It's
writing it is d se form
Right
So one
It's
n target
I want it's not dat
zero
What do you do it
turn
valid option
You mini options it
You can have
valid option
You mini options it
You can have
valid option
You mini options it
You can have
reduced the probability
Of action
Didn't take
n time
It's n probability distribution
Right
When
It's n probability distribution
Right
When
It's n probability distribution
Right
When
I reduce the probability
This is
automatic
You have to take out
This note
Like I am
automatic
You have to take out
This note
Like I am
automatic
You have to take out
This note
Like I am
rewarding action and take
Right
Dat
rewarding action and take
Right
Dat
rewarding action and take
Right
Dat
They have this constraint of probability
How you some one way bill automatically reward
d other action okay so but not alpha and beta
so defending on d relationship between
alpha and beta so you have different kids of
algorithm
right equal
tu bita so they have something called
so something called linear reward penalty
LRP algorithm okay so it's it's this these things have been
around per
money dickens okay so d LRP
algorithm it's really every because d
relationship dat is which is linear so you can see dat are
no higher order terms in the update
so so you do something you change d parameter
on n reward and also change d parameter
when you get n penalty right so what is it
plus one penalty zero and your changing
them brother equal amounts right dat is when
alpha equal tu b time so when alpha
- 2 and something like and two I right
give
confirmation tomorrow
relaxation I don't nothing I just
please d
probability
Self
changing these things around turns of d
convergence behavior of these three
algorithms so very different
and defending on ho ho rewarding your
answer
per example me best am late se hyderabad is so
small
d penalty side i always be depressing
me|  Probability
p penalty
things like this so this
was this style a very vibrant
community date work with this kind of
learning automatic history and this is the most basic
most fundamental of this one
things I told you about this very I bill
structure
automatic
used on solving so this is a kind of
calculation of d variable structure an
financial statement so you mean you can do
and write it more explicitly today you
have it turns out you be automatic right but
this is more of a compact way of
presenting friend variable automatic so I am not going to get in you match it you you
dire this vibrant community date ten this right
and so this is just tell you date this
history of using this policy
representation directly right goes back
several d kids in fact earliest set
learning automatic was proposed in the 1930s
devotional approaches and provided sum of d value
function value  Estimate based approaches
October okay
so
taking this father
of coming up
d policy update and sims very natural way
of doing it same I get an award and
chris n probability okay if I get a
penalty degree from probability science like very
natural way have you get per sir
most systematic way of thinking about
learning d policies directly right so it's very
[praise]
and
increase direction which is receiving lot of
attention tomorrow
policy gradient approaches d book calls
this
parameter policy representation will you know
value function based method like give de
tomorrow this a
parameter policy approaches so d basic
idea every is I am going to home date me
policy it right so every I am giving you d
policies it n probability values ​​right some
good night policies depends on
policy depends on some set of parameters
okay mean by this so
me policy is an probability
distribution right I can specify d
probability  Distribution in anyways per
example
right so specified by function
what is it what I need so give you in what
out you define d policy
right so suppose I am saying date I need you tell you
what d softmax function is
corresponding to my current policy right so
what is it information date I should
communicate in
d right per action I have something I put
in exponent I love you tell you date right it
they bill not be values ​​just remember
date I just talking about d
softmax function right however I derive
d value date goes in exponent it
can be an value function it can be something else right I have just
I bill
try out some number I have said action
one put n three in d exponent ok
action you put n 15 in exponent action 3
put 22 and exponent ok just give you
friend numbers arbitrary but this define
Policy and however arrived friend number this
define
parameter is representation so I have d
set of parameter okay date define d policy
it is so this is it sleep what you mean by
parameter so they have an set of per I me se they jump b anything they
jump b solid values
come a plug in you the exponents which some
times are called
preferences okay right
so I can just say prefer action
this you action b right and give I can have some sort
of converting date did actual
probability and I say I preference per
action has 25 I preference per action piece
13 right and from date I can convert because in
value has an separate se
romantic associated with right d values ​​se
expected pay of d time going you get
on pulling da when I say preference per d
23 date and have necessary have other se
romantic so 23 versus 15 so 23 higher than
15 is right  Note necessity date 23 main date
this is d pay off I am going to get so this give
me a lot more flexibility and how I
change it need not
necessity of the expectation okay right so it
jump by preference it jump by
weight of a neural network
it is something
which of you should be thinking about
ho money periods article about co
playing agent
one you three four five six seven people everybody
read d co playing agent
what alpha co goal co ko you google search
alpha co
and d Hindu crying out lo so this is this
machine learning agent with you know actually specify exactly
what
it is d machine learning algorithm used and
learning agent dat learns you play this game
of co which per an long long time was
considered one of the hardest games per
computer you play because d number of
pattern sets you should have and just right and the
rules are very simple but give turn  of you be very
very hard game on computer you play
definitely not at human levels right but let's
google deep man has come up so let's
google deep should know what algorithm date you
sir okay what at all what ho they
formulated d problem right so let's
read it first learning and deep neural
network n train it actually beat d
European champion five zero
player series of five matches and it d
happy and jo five of dem
right and dewar hopping you have an match up with
d world champion co player in march
and some dates march
world champion because apparently world
champion player is a match higher level de jo d other place out dewar
but style it
dewar is home right so d point is l plus
neural networks science you be the hot think no this right so everybody wants to do it so this is
note n it's note an
example okay if you are going to beat d
dewar and do reinforce learning this is
Probability what you bill and up doing right so
where d parameter but they are generated by
neural network right and I bill give you another
example so and this you can think of
parameter on this representation
you so what kind of an probability
distribution
trailer
so what is this d equal and version of
varionaly
actually mention this in animal class which
I am not talking about the conjugate
value just I am saying on repeated
experiment you outcome repeated
experiment is binomial single trial is
binomial
experiment is
categorical
distribution total d categorical kil
distribution this is essentially multiple
outcome single experiment probability
distribution okay but of d parameter
describe bin oil distribution
probability so date so this is it again one way
you have to think about this this is also
an parameter distribution
where I am specifying directly the
parameter of the
multi  Binomial in this how I just said
this love I jump from which April note equal
you 80 and give fat just this alpha give I
basically made it in normal how so
this is also an private thing I jump
specify other kind of distribution
like this right just like they did here I am
going to
modify the policy parameter directly
right in modify the value functions and
what it be an systematic way of doing this you can come up with these
things right so but
I am talking about an great in best
approach
[Music]